;; ;; have items like 

;; (cash-value-on-person <PERSON> <AMOUNT>)
;; (value-in-bank-account <ACCOUNT> <AMOUNT>)
;; ;; and have an action

;; (withdraw-cash-from-bank-account <PERSON> <ACCOUNT> <LOCATION> <AMOUNT>)
;; (deposit-cash-to-bank-account <PERSON> <ACCOUNT> <LOCATION> <AMOUNT>)

;; (is-bank <LOCATION> <BANKNAME>)

;; have a GUI interface for adding persons, bank accounts, locations,
;; etc, use the SPSE2 system for graphically modelling such items

;; add a paypal transfer mechanism

